

About Me

Skilled professional working to improve the corporate learning process through creative instructional design, engaging and fun training sessions, and thoughtful tailor-made training programs.

Skills

- Creative Problem Solving
- Change Management
- Content Creation
- Data-Driven Decision Making and Analysis
- Emotional Intelligence
- Instructional Design
- Product Implementation
- Project Management
- Training (Virtual & In-Person)

Software Experience

- Adobe Captivate
- Adobe Connect
- Adobe and Nuance Power PDF
- Camtasic
- Concep
- Google Suite
- GoToMeeting
- InSided
- Lesson.ly LMS
- MailChimp
- Microsoft Teams
- One Note
- Pendo Guide Creation
- SkillJar LMS
- UniversitySite LMS
- WebEx
- Zoom

mrs.amanda.koski@gmail.com 815.814.3846 Linkedin.com/in/aarient

Amanda Koski

Portfolio

Please visit my portfolio page for more information, work samples, storyboards, and project plans. https://ahkoski.github.io/index.html

Work Experience



eLEARNING & Product Enablement Expert, RECIPROCITY INC

2021 - present

I am a project manager within the content team, meeting with stakeholders, planning out content calendars, and developing learning material for our internal and external users. I also own and manage the LMS for internal users, customers, and partners.

- Launched a new LMS: Lead the launch of a new learning management system platform (SkillJar) which included the planning, prep, design, and release of Reciprocity University. RU contains three separate domains to manage, customerfacing, internal, and partner-facing. I am also a member of the leadership committee owning the launch of our Customer Portal and continue to be a vital member of this team.
- Managed Learning Initiative: Lead a team that has been planning and began
 creating new learning material surrounding the launch of a brand new product.
 This included working with internal stakeholders, coordinating with various teams
 and subject-matter experts, and scheduling time for the teams to begin content
 creation. This project is currently underway.
- Designed new Onboarding: Created an innovative plan for internal onboarding at Reciprocity, which included working with various departments to discover the program's needs, map out the success criteria, and have begun building out content with the applicable subject matter experts.

🖄 п

LEARNING DESIGN SPECIALIST, FOLEY & LARDNER

2020 - 2021

I was a learning artificer, creating new and engaging learning content. I worked with subject matter experts in various departments to produce relevant, helpful, and engaging training modules.

- **Established Incoming Project Process:** I utilized Microsoft Power Automate, Microsoft Teams, and Microsoft Forms to create a seamless process for our team to receive incoming project requests from various departments.
- Email Systems Manager: Subject matter expert and admin for our department's email marketing system (Concep). I designed, created, and sent out all internal communications from our department. This includes creating and executing communication plans for various learning projects and our new hire correspondences.
- **Branding Consultant:** Designed all video branding for our department and several other departments within the firm.
- Lead designer of Enrichment Program: I was the lead designer of a project called the "Assistant Enrichment Program," where I was involved in the conception, development, and creation of gamified assessments to evaluate the assistant population of approx. 260 users on basic skills they should possess as a legal assistant
- Boys and Girls Club Relationship Committee: A member of the committee that works with our local Boys and Girls Club to plan events, fundraise, collect donations, and complete service work.

Certifications

- eLearning Instructional Design (ATD)
- Technical Writing (University of WI)
- MOS Excel Expert (Microsoft)
- MOS Word Expert (Microsoft)
- MOS PPT Specialist (Microsoft)
- MOS Outlook Specialist (Microsoft)
- MOS Office Master 2016 (Microsoft)

Education

Marauette University Class of 2013

Bachelor of Science

Mathematics and Secondary Education

Special Programs:

Residence Life, Students Taking Active Roles, and CommUNITY

References

Nedesha Coleman

Manager of Learning & Development, Folev & Lardner 804.319.5574

Leigh Ann Whitmarsh

Former Director of Customer Experience, Reciprocity Inc. 907.299.7705

Please contact me if additional references are needed.

Work Experience (cont.)



SR. TECHNOLOGY LEARNING COACH, FOLEY & LARDNER

I was a leader in training and technology implementation within a law firm. I worked to promote a technology-first approach to education and designed new and innovative learning materials while conducting fun, engaging training sessions in-person, via video conference, and live virtual training across 24 offices and for 2,500 employees Worldwide.

- Designed Up-to-Date New Hire Orientation Programs: Integral member of a project team that constantly looks to revamp and streamline our New Hire Orientation Programs that onboard over 500 new employees a year.
- Subject Matter Expert: Supervised the training of all admin users for the release of a new reservation software to the law firm, as well as participated in countless other rollouts for the firm. This included insight on decisions regarding implementation and configuration and in-person training, and floor support.
- Spearheaded Email Automation Project: Spearheaded a project team that evaluated, tested, and recommended the purchase of a new piece of software for the firm. Once purchased, I was charged with designing the workflows surrounding the latest software and training all other users.

IMPLEMENTATION SPECIALIST, ADVICENT SOLUTIONS

As an implementation specialist, I was a mix of an Instructional Designer, a Project Manager, and a Corporate Trainer. I worked to design meaningful training materials while also delivering an excellent training experience through live virtual training sessions and pre-recorded videos.

- Project Manager: Collaborated with team members to onboard each new incoming client while offering them training to best suit their individual needs.
- Engagement Committee Member: Encouraged active participation and positive company engagement.
- · Innovation Team: Lead an Innovation Team to improve the Customer Onboarding experience through internal workflow adjustments and external communication.
- · Organizational Readiness Team: Key member of the Org Readiness Team, working cross-departmentally with a common goal, prepare the organization for each release of a new version of our software.



PARTNER SUPPORT SPECIALIST, ADVICENT SOLUTIONS

2015 - 2016

I excelled at an internal help desk position for a software company partnered with financial institutions worldwide. I assisted customers with support for Advicent software through phone and email communications.

- Enterprise Case Owner: Representative from the company paired with a large enterprise customer to ensure their experiences are pleasant and all of their needs are met. I established a new workflow to specifically meet the needs of the customers I worked with.
- New Hire Mentor: Mentored over 20 new hires during 1 year.
- Engagement Committee Member: Encouraged active participation and positive company engagement.



SALES PROGRAM ANALYST, UNICARRIERS AMERICAS

I managed a sales database that worked to approve or deny discount applications to varying sales programs. This encompassed meeting with internal stakeholders, updating and owning the information within the database, running reports to ensure sales metrics were being met, and running macros through Microsoft Access to push data to various departments.



MATHEMATICS TEACHER, WISCONSIN AREA SCHOOLS

I used innovative education practices by operating a flipped classroom and introduced new and exciting technology to both students and faculty that improved student engagement, and educated students and enabled them to become problem solvers using logic and deductive reasoning.

mrs.amanda.koski@gmail.com 815.814.3846 Linkedin.com/in/aarient